Santander NC B-LOC
, Fc O
25 Z O
may NC O
( Fpa O
EFE NC B-ORG
) Fpt O
. Fp O

EFE NC B-ORG
- Fg O
Cantabria VMI B-LOC
Fráncfort AQ B-LOC
( Fpa O
RFA NP B-LOC
) Fpt O
, Fc O
25 Z O
may NC O
( Fpa O
EFECOM NP B-ORG
) Fpt O
. Fp O
